A shiny glass collage of Pixar characters comes together in triangle shapes.
The Pixar world has a blue sky and fluffy clouds with shining stars.
Pixar character silhouettes fade in, encircled with twinkling stars, against a galactic background.
Dory is revealed!
Dory and Lightning McQueen are revealed!
Pixar character silhouettes fade in, encircled with twinkling stars, against a galactic background.
Dory, Lightning McQueen and Elastigirl are revealed!
Dory, Lightning McQueen, Elastigirl and Woody are revealed!
Pixar character silhouettes fade in, encircled with twinkling stars, against a galactic background.
Dory, Lightning McQueen, Elastigirl, Woody and Miguel are revealed!
Dory, Lightning McQueen, Elastigirl, Woody, Miguel and Meilin are revealed!
Pixar character silhouettes fade in, encircled with twinkling stars, against a galactic background.
Dory, Lightning McQueen, Elastigirl, Woody, Miguel, Meilin and Joy are revealed!